<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="redirect_scheme">readtracker</string>

  <string name="enter_page_count">Please enter the number of pages or toggle percent tracking</string>

  <string name="textOn">ON</string>
  <string name="textOff">OFF</string>

  <string name="associate_anonymous_readings">Do you want to associate the %s existing readings on this device with your
    Readmill account?
  </string><string name="asd">Spent a total of 19 hours and 45 minutes\nOver 38 reading sessions.</string>

  <string name="delete_reading_connected">This will DELETE the book, both from your device AND from your Readmill profile.\n\nAll related data such as highlights and progress will also be delete.\n\nThere is NO WAY to restore it.</string>
  <string name="delete_reading_unconnected">This will DELETE the book from your device.\n\nAll related data such as highlights and progress will also be delete.\n\nThere is NO WAY to restore it.</string>
  <string name="welcome_tagline">Helps you get all your reading into your Readmill account</string>
  <string name="welcome_text">ReadTracker is a tool for syncing any book you are reading with your Readmill account.\n\nReadmill is a web service that helps you leave a trail of the books you\'ve read and loved, together highlights of the parts that was most important to you.\n\nAnd with Readmill you can share this with your friends, or follow interesting people who can inspire you to find the next book to read.</string>
  <string name="readmill_shared">Book will be visible on your Readmill profile. Friends who follow you will see when you
    start reading, finish reading or create highlights.\n\nYour activity might also be shared to Facebook or Twitter depending on what you have activated for your Readmill account.
  </string>

  <string name="readmill_private">Book will be visible only to you on your Readmill profile.\n\nNo one else can see that you are reading it, and nothing is ever shared to other services like Facebook and Twitter.</string>

</resources>
